Kirito!
Um, Yori?
Thank you.
And welcome back, Kirito.
Sorry I took so long, and for
making you worry about me.
Thank you, Alice.
No, Kirito, wait!
Don't worry, he'll be fine.
We just have to have faith
in him, but we better hurry.
We don't have much time left here.
Asuna!
Don't worry. I... I'm okay.
The altar's closing.
I have to get you out.
Kirito, I have so many questions,
and even more to tell you.
You must prevail, triumph over
that demon, and come back to me.
I love you so far.
I don't think I'm going to die.
Higa says if you're still in there
when we reach maximum acceleration,
by the time we disconnect you here,
200 years will have passed there.
All right, who are you?
I'm a hunter and a thief and a destroyer.
So what are you doing here?
I'm hunting souls
And who are you?
Why are you here?
What gives you the right
to stand in my way?
My name...
My name is...
You're Kirito.
Kirito the swordsman.
My name is Kirito.
Now it's your turn.
I'm Gabriel.
Gabriel Miller. Mr. Swordsman.
Let's go, Gabriel!
Generate all elements!
Discharge!
it should take those two
about five minutes to
reach the system console
you You have three minutes.
Try not to bore me too much.
You're so generous with your time.
Three minutes?
That's all I'll need.
Hmph.
Thanks for the idea.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Up to now all I cared about was fighting
long enough so Asuna
and Alice could get out.
I was okay with getting
stuck here for 200 years
but now I'm wondering why
is it because deep down
I want to stay I mean
this is what I hope for a
true alternate world
bigger and better and more?
real than Aincrad.
I didn't think what that'd do to
Asuna, Alice, my family and friends.
How back
home they'd cry over me while I
lived here until my soul fizzled out.
Did I ever care about how
they felt?
Am I that selfish?
No, you're not.
You wanting to stay here
isn't for selfish reasons.
Friends, that's not the Kirito I know.
You care about the Underworld,
and the people you met here.
But that's not true of him.
He doesn't care about anyone at all.
He's incapable.
That's why he hunts, and
steals, and destroys.
It's cause he's scared.
Scared of people.
I know what he's feeling now.
On the brink of death, his confidence
has failed him. He's afraid.
I think I'll have a taste.
I'll feast on your feelings, your
memories, your mind, your soul.
I'll gobble them all up.
Good luck, asshole.
You won't find any of them there.
My body's just a vessel. I'll...
I'll show you where my soul's at! What?
Police, speckle auction!
It's him.
His heart, his soul, his everything.
Please.
Let all of me reach Kirito, too.
Kazutou.
I'm sending all the strength I
have left to you, big brother.
I'm starting to wonder,
what's all of this mean?
You know, like to have
power and to be strong.
You already know.
Just search your heart.
The answer is right there.
A power greater than anger or hate.
Kirito, I have a confession to make.
I really do love Kirito.
That makes two of us.
Our souls are connected, so
we're always with you, Kirito.
Even now.
I see now, to live, to struggle, to
rise, to connect hearts and lives.
They are what it means to be strong.
They are proof of it.
Eugeo, hear my prayer.
Please protect my sister and Kirito.
Thank you.
Kirito!
Though my soul has existed only a
short while as a fraudulent night,
I know without a doubt
these feelings I have,
these emotions surging
within me, are real!
Katie Doe.
Oh, my God.
Reject your urge to kill,
for that man's empty soul cannot be
slashed by an incarnation of murder.
If you're scared, kid, don't be.
With the swing of your sword,
the weight of this world will
come crashing down on him.
Now, boy, show me your resolve.
My divine willpower is now
yours to wield as you see fit.
Chirito, you must believe.
Believe in the hearts of
all the people you love,
and know they all love you in return.
Stormcast Stream!
It's over!
Get me out!
Go on.
Here's your chance.
End it.
Thank you, Yujiho.
You can't satisfy my
hunger with this light.
I'll devour it like everything else.
Like hell you will.
The power of the human
heart scares you most.
And now you'll choke on it.
LAUGHTER
I don't know.
Thank you.
Bye you, Jill.
Thanks again.
Thank God, they both logged out in time.
Hope you like my world, Alice.
The next 200 years should be interesting.
Asuna, Xenon, Leafa, everyone.
But...
I didn't go.
Asuna.
Thank you.
Next time, The Time of Time.